kamiyabiomedical.com 2019-07-18

# PRIVACY POLICY

PRIVACY POLICY
KAMIYA BIOMEDICAL COMPANY (and collectively, "KAMIYA", "we", "us" or "our") takes your
privacy seriously. This privacy policy describes how we collect, use and disclose your personal
information in connection with you doing business with us, and in using our websites (Sites)
www.k-assay.com and www.kamiyabiomedical.com.
By using our Sites and doing business with us, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure
of your personal information as outlined in this policy. Your consent is the legal basis for our use
of your personal information. You can withdraw your consent at any time. However, if you
withdraw your consent to certain uses, we may no longer be able to provide our products and
services to you.
Our Company Activities
We are a B2B (business to business) seller of biomedical products. We do not typically sell to
individual consumers. Our data collection activities are limited to using the information provided
to us by our customers in order to facilitate the ordering process and to notify you of new
products and services that we may offer.
Who We Collect Information From
We collect personal information from:
    •   individuals who establish a relationship with us by telephone, fax, or email, and who
        provide us with personal information;
    •   distributors who request that we ship a product directly to a particular individual.
What Personal Information We Collect
We may collect personal information which includes:
    •   contact information that you send to us via email, fax, or mail, or provide to us over the
        phone, such as your name, title, employer name, work address, work email address and
        phone numbers;
    •   purchase and sale transaction information such as your credit card information, products
        and services ordered, and the details of your transaction;
    •   your current geographic location.
Special Categories of Personal Data
We do not request, obtain, or process special categories of data, namely, sensitive personal
data that reveal racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, or
trade union membership, and the processing of genetic data, biometric data for the purpose of
uniquely identifying a natural person, data concerning health, or data concerning a natural
person’s sex life or sexual orientation.
How We Use Personal Information
We will only collect and use your personal information for the following purposes, except as
permitted or required by applicable law:
                                                  1

     •   communicating with you by email, mail and phone to handle any inquiries that you have
         made to us;
     •   processing orders that you have submitted to us;
     •   to provide customer and technical service;
     •   acknowledging your comments and/or replying to your questions, complaints and
         requests;
     •   communicating with you and providing you with information on and direct marketing of
         our products and services that we believe may be of interest to you;
     •   to serve advertisements to you in various marketing channels, including but not limited to
         direct mail;
     •   generally managing and administering our business;
     •   preventing and prosecuting fraud and/or credit risk;
     •   meeting legal and regulatory requirements.
Limited to Disclosed Purposes
We limit the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information to that which is needed to
achieve the above noted purposes.
Who We Disclose Personal Information To
We will only disclose your personal information in the following circumstances, except as
permitted or required by applicable law:
     •   to our Distributors, as necessary to provide you with the products and services that you
         have requested or to fulfill the transactions you have submitted;
     •   to third party companies and contractors that provide us with services in the conduct of
         our business ("service providers"), such as shipping companies and payment processing
         companies, but only as necessary for those service providers to provide services to us;
     •   to third parties as we deem necessary or appropriate to prevent, limit or otherwise
         prosecute fraud;
     •   as necessary to meet legal and regulatory requirements; and
     •   any other circumstance in which you provide consent to disclose.
Service Providers
All KAMIYA service providers are contractually bound to keep your information secure. Our
service providers can use, store and disclose your personal information solely for purposes for
which it is disclosed to them (to provide us with services).
Other Data Protection Laws and Privacy Policies Impacting Personal Data
KAMIYA, our Distributors, and our service providers are located in various jurisdictions including,
among others, the United States and the European Union and, as a result, your personal
information may be stored, processed or transferred into or out of these countries. The data
protection laws in these countries may be different to those in your country and your information
may be subject to access by the regulatory authorities in, and to the laws of, those other
jurisdictions.
Data Retention
We will retain your personal information for as long as
                                                    2

    •   your account is active;
    •   your personal information is needed to provide you products or services; or
    •   it is necessary to meet legal, regulatory, insurance and audit requirements.
If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide
you products or services, contact ordering@k-assay.com
Accuracy of Your Personal Information
We will use commercially reasonable efforts to ensure that your personal information is correct,
complete and up-to-date to the extent we are notified of any changes by you. You can review
and update your personal information by contacting us. You can assist by keeping us informed
of any changes or informing us if you find any errors in our information about you. If we have
disclosed inaccurate information about you to a third party that you are aware of, please to
contact the third party in order to correct the information upon your request.
Your Rights with Respect to Your Personal Information
If you wish to change any of your personal information we have on file in our records, you may
contact us as noted at the bottom of this page. To protect your privacy and security, we may
take reasonable steps to verify your identity prior to making corrections.
You are entitled to be informed or and have access to any of your personal information in our
custody or control. Upon written request, we will provide you with your personal information
under our custody or control, as well as information regarding how your personal information is
being used and the identity of any third party(s) to whom that information has been disclosed.
Please note that we may not be able to provide access to personal information in certain
circumstances, such as if the personal information was collected for the purposes of an
investigation, if disclosure would reveal the personal information of a third party, or if prohibited
by law. To protect your privacy and security, we may take reasonable steps to verify your
identity prior to providing such access.
Rights of European Data Subjects
In addition to rights with respect to your personal data already noted elsewhere in this policy, for
those individuals residing in the European Economic Area, you have certain additional rights
under the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):
Restrictions on Further Processing
You have the right, where there is a dispute in relation to the accuracy or basis of processing of
your personal data, to request a restriction on further processing by us.
Erasure
You have the right to erasure of your personal data (“right to be forgotten”) in certain
circumstances.
Data Portability
You have the right to request that personal data that you have provided to us be returned to
you, or be provided to another third party of your choice, in a structured, commonly used and
machine-readable format.
                                                    3

Automated Decision-Making
You have the right not to be subject to a decision based solely on automated decision-making.
In connection with such right, you may have the right to request human intervention with respect
to such automated decision-making, as well as express your point of view or contest any such
automated decision-making.
Opt-out of Direct Marketing / Profiling
You may elect to “opt out” of direct marketing activities, including any profiling we may conduct
for direct marketing purposes. Accordingly, we may rely on your consent permitting us to
process your information in accordance with this policy for direct marketing, including profiling
for direct marketing, unless you take affirmative action to opt out of such processing. You may
opt out at any time by contacting us, as provided further below.
Lodge Complaints with Supervisory Authorities
You have the right to lodge a complaint with a data protection supervisory authority in your
country.
Cookies, JSON Web Tokens, Clear Gifs
We do not use cookies, JSON web tokens, or clear gifs (also known as tracking pixels) on our
Sites.
Links to Third Party Sites
We may provide links or references to third party sites whose privacy practices may differ from
those of KAMIYA BIOMEDICAL COMPANY. You may also navigate to our Site through a link from a
Partner or other third party site. KAMIYA BIOMEDICAL COMPANY assumes no responsibility for
the content or the privacy policies of those Partner or third party websites. Please be aware that
when you follow any links to another site not owned or operated by KAMIYA BIOMEDICAL
COMPANY to any of those sites, you are subject to their privacy policies. We encourage you to
carefully read the privacy policy of any website you visit.
Social Media Features
Our Sites does not include any social media features.
Security Measures
We take reasonable measures, including administrative, physical and technical safeguards, to
protect your information from loss, theft, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and
destruction.     We store your personal information using validated security measures.
Nevertheless, we cannot absolutely guarantee that unauthorized third parties will never be able
to defeat our security measures or use your personal information for improper purposes. In the
event that your personal information in our possession or under our control is compromised as a
result of a security breach, we will take reasonable steps to investigate the situation and, where
appropriate, notify you and take other steps in accordance with applicable laws or regulations.
Remember that email sent over the Internet is generally unencrypted and transmitted in clear
text. We recommend that you use caution when forwarding free-format email messages to us
                                                 4

and that you do not include confidential information in those messages. Confidential information
should be transmitted to us through other secure methods such as by telephone or fax.
Revision of Policy
This policy may be revised from time to time. We will notify you of material changes prior to
such material change being effective by a prominent notice on our website. Your continued use
of our website shall constitute your acceptance of the revised policy. We encourage you to
periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.
Disputes and Complaints
This policy is subject to our Terms of Use, including terms regarding the governing law and the
resolution of any disputes between you and KAMIYA BIOMEDICAL COMPANY.
If you have a complaint with respect to our privacy policy, please contact us as provided below.
Contacting Us
If you have questions, comments or complaints with respect to our privacy policy or if you wish
to request access to, or correction or deletion of your personal information under KAMIYA’s care
and control, please contact us at:
ordering@k-assay.com
KAMIYA BIOMEDICAL COMPANY
12779 Gateway Drive S.
Seattle, WA 98168
U.S.A.
+1 206-575-8068
KAMIYA will respond to your request for access in accordance with applicable privacy legislation.
This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 29, 2018.
                                                   5
